[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Maggies nickname in the 1958 movie Cat on a Hot Tin Roof?", "correct_answer": "The Cat", "incorrect_answers": ["The Bunny", "The Tigress", "The Swallow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sams sister Ginny is having menstrual cramps right before her wedding in Sixteen Candles. What does she take to relieve the pain?", "correct_answer": "muscle relaxants", "incorrect_answers": ["Vodka", "Midol", "a bunch of aspirin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color eyes do male box turtles commonly have?", "correct_answer": "red", "incorrect_answers": ["blue", "green", "black"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Moa was unique because even though it was a bird it had no wings.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played  the female lead in Sleepless in Seattle?", "correct_answer": "Meg Ryan", "incorrect_answers": ["Parker Posey", "Rita Wilson", "Kim Basinger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Singer Johnny Cash was very close to his older brother Jack, who died in an accident involving what?", "correct_answer": "Table Saw", "incorrect_answers": ["Shotgun", "Tractor", "Wagon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which film is memorable for this quote?\nNow back up, put the gun down, and get me a pack of Tropical Fruit Bubblicious.", "correct_answer": "Bad Boys", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue Streak", "Bad Boys II", "National Security"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If a beverage has mocha in the name, what ingredients can you be sure that it contains?", "correct_answer": "Chocolate, coffee and milk", "incorrect_answers": ["Milk, sugar and coffee", "Sugar and coffee", "Milk and chocolate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Major League Baseball player, whose uniform with #42 was retired on April 15, 1997 by Major League Baseball, became the first African-American to be inducted into the Baseball Hall of Fame.", "correct_answer": "Jack Roosevelt Robinson", "incorrect_answers": ["Rosy Grier", "Jim Brown", "Jesse Owens"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When the FBI raids the house in the movie Point Break, one suspect ends up shooting himself in the foot. The actor playing this character is better known as the lead singer of what famous group?", "correct_answer": "Red Hot Chili Peppers", "incorrect_answers": ["Danzig", "Metallica", "Stone Temple Pilots"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which US state hosts a carrot festival in the town that calls itself Carrot Capital of the World?", "correct_answer": "California", "incorrect_answers": ["Texas", "Florida", "Utah"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not among the traditional ingredients used for the making of the Japanese dish Nikujaga?", "correct_answer": "Seaweed", "incorrect_answers": ["Meat", "Onions", "Potatoes"]}]